>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 让我们谈谈另一个特殊的价值。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Let's talk
about another special value.
这个看起来很奇怪，因为地球上的东西是负零吗 ?
This one seems rather strange because
what on Earth is a negative zero?
如果你问一个数学家的话，他们会说那是不存在的，
If you ask a mathematician, they'll say
that's made up, that doesn't exist,
那不是真的
that's not a real thing.
它确实存在于编程中，它绝对存在于 IEEE 754中。
It definitely exists in programming,
it definitely exists in IEEE 754.
就像在 IEEE 754 中存在的楠一样，但一个数学家却不知道什么是 nan 意味着什么。
Just like nan exists in IEEE 754, but a
mathematician doesn't know what nan means.
那肯定也需要 IEEE 54 如果你愿意的话，
Then it definitely also requires,
IEEE 54 if you will,
需要有一个负零。
requires there to be a negative zero.
那么，这意味着什么 ?
So, what does that mean?
它本质上是零值，但是有符号位。
Well, it's essentially the zero value,
but with the sign bit on.
因此，它是零的负表示。
So it is the negative
representation of a zero.
现在， JavaScript 的早期认为 JavaScript 开发者永远不会
Now, early days of JavaScript felt
that JavaScript developers would never
想要一个负的零
want a negative zero.
所以他们在极端的长度上试图假扮
And so they actually went to extreme
lengths to try to pretend as if it didn't
我们会看到一群古怪的人
exist which we're gonna see
a whole bunch of weirdness.
例如，如果将 -0 指定为 trendRate 第 1 行，
For example, if I have a -0
assigned to trendRate line 1,
我和我的三等同音都是真的听起来很棒
here and I triple equals it with
-0 I get true, sounds great.
如果我把它扼杀了怎么办
What happens if I stringify it?
我在这里用 toString 方法还有别的办法但是如果我把它
I'll use the toString method here,
there's other ways, but if I stringify it,
我有 0
I get 0.
那不是好事对吧
That's not good, right?
0我的负号在哪里
0, where's my negative sign?
JavaScript 的早期咒语感觉像是 JavaScript 开发者会认为
The early incantation of JavaScript felt
like JavaScript developers would think
它是一只虫子如果你带了一个 0 然后把它串化，然后在绳子上得到 -0 .
that it was a bug if you took a -0 and
stringified it and got -0 in the string.
感觉就像一个像一只虫子一样的最终用户
It felt like that would look
to the end user like a bug,
而 JavaScript 会被指责
and JavaScript would get blamed.
我觉得回想，语言应该做正确的事，
I think in retrospect,
languages should do the correct thing and
就是开发商做一些对用户合理的事情。
it's on developers to do something
that's reasonable to users.
语言不应该步进，并尝试对其开发者进行第二次猜测。
Languages should not step in and
try to second guess their developers.
在 JavaScript 中存在着一些历史上的怪异
And there's a bunch of the historical
weirdness in JavaScript where
他们尝试了各种不同的理由让他们更容易接受
they tried for
various reasons to be more palatable.
我们得到了自动的半结肠插入和整个其他的东西
We get automatic semi colon insertion and
a whole, whole host of other things
那里的语言试图让开发者很聪明
where the language trying
to out smart the developer.
事实证明，开发人员并不聪明。
And it turns out don't
out smart the developer.
让他们做他们能用合理的合理一致
Just let them do what they can with
the sensible reasonable coherent
工具的集合好吗
set of tools, okay?
好吧那两条线就在我们之间
Okay, so the two string lies to us and
by the way,
三等也等于我们， cus 它说 -0 等于 0 。
the triple equals also lies to us,
cuz it says the -0 is equal to a 0.
同时， -0 也不小于 0 或大于 0。
And in also -0 is neither less than 0 or
greater than 0.
因此，我感到遗憾的是 :
So, the less than and the less than or
equal and the greater, I'm sorry,
比具体要少的多
the less than and
a greater than specifically,
他们撒谎， > 凯尔 - 辛普森: 他们都在撒谎
they lie
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: They all lie.
所以很长一段时间我们都没有真正的建立
So for a long time we didn't really have
a built in way of determining if we had
一 0，你可以得到 0 ，但是你不能确定你有一个。
a -0, you could get -0s, but
you couldn't determine that you had one.
在 ES6 之前，他们添加了一个名为 object.is的实用程序。
Until ES6 they added
a utility called object.is,
我想说的是这就像四叉一样
object.is, I like to refer to this
as like the quadruple equals.
人们喜欢在双平等的问题上开玩笑，它能让所有这些不同的
People like to joke about how double
equals, it allows all these different
强迫我们去做一个质量的过程
coercions and stuff we'll get into
a course of a quality in bit.
他们喜欢讲双平等的笑话
They like to joke about
double equals is changing and
三等同值是精确的除了几个谎言之外
triple equals is exact,
it's strict except for a couple of lies.
如果我们不希望那些谎言再加上一个平等的谎言
Well, if we don't want those lies
let's just add another equals on, so
就像这里的第四个等号
it's like the fourth equals here.
它根本不撒谎，如果是 -0，如果是真的，如果不是的话，它就不存在了。
It doesn't lie at all, if it's a -0,
if it's true and otherwise, it doesn't.
如果是 0 ，它会给你真实或其他的，我的意思是，
And if it's a zero,
it gives you true or otherwise, I mean,
否则就不知道了
false or otherwise it doesn't.
那是你唯一的选择如果你想考零号
So that's your only option,
if you wanna test for the zero.
事实上有个数学运算
Actually, there's technically
a mathematical operation and
那是个暗示
that's a hint for later.
有一个可以用来确定 -0的数学运算。
There is a mathematical operation
that you can use to determine -0.
但在大多数情况下，最好的方法是使用内置的检查器和
But for the most part, the best way to do
this is to use this built-in checker and
通过此方法，可以使用 object.is 来检查名称。
by the way,
object.is can be used to check names.
虽然我说 number.is 是一个比较语义的工具，但是
Although I would say number.is is
a more semantic tool for it, but
也可以使用 object.is。
you can also use object.is.
所以现在你在问自己
So now you're asking yourself,
好吧这奇怪的微妙问题没人在乎对吧
okay great, there's this weird nuanced
thing that no one cares about, right?
谁会在乎负零呢 ?
Who would even care about a negative zero?
我觉得他们是合法的
Well, I think they
are legitimate purposes,
我之前在我的节目中使用了负面的零。
I have actually use negative
zeros in my programs before.
从数学上来说我们是指两个独立的实体
Mathematically it's very common for
us to refer to two separate entities or
两个特征在同一个数字值中分隔。
two separates characteristics
in the same numeric value.
例如，数字的绝对值表示
For example, the absolute value
of the number represents for
比如有多快的事情会发生
example how fast something
might be moving.
而这个符号代表了它的前进方向。
And the sign represents
what direction it's moving.
说你在地图上有车这就是我所拥有的
Say you've got a little car on a map and
this is actually what I had.
我在一家公司工作，在那里构建了这个映射解决方案，
I worked in a company where we
built this mapping solution, and
我们有辆小车在地图上移动
we had this little car
that moved around a map.
我需要知道车是这样还是这样移动的。
And I needed to know whether the car
was moving this way or this way.
我把它停在什么方向
What direction do I make
it look when it stops?
我想让它看起来是在它停止之前的同一方向。
Well, I wanted to make it look in the same
direction that it was before it stopped.
如何确定一个数字，是什么方向，如果是零，
How do I determine what one number,
what direction it was, if at zero,
我们失去信号了吗
we lose the sign?
所以负零其实是有用的，我用的是游戏的
So negative zero was actually useful
there, and I use those in games for
非常相似的目的。
very similar purposes.
所以我们的潮流，就像这个例子一样，就是
So our trendRate,
as the going example goes, is that
我可以用这个号码的标志有一个叫 math.sign的实用程序
I could use the sign of this number,
there's a utility called math.sign,
这件事应该告诉我们这个东西没有符号
which is supposedly gonna tell us is this
thing doesn't have the sign bit or not.
如果我们有一个负零点，那就应该可以告诉我们。
And that should have been able to
tell us if we had a negative zero.
不幸的是他们做了一些超级愚蠢的事情
Unfortunately, that went and did
something super dumb which was that they
使 math.sign 返回负零和零，而不返回负 1 和 1。
made math.sign return negative zero and
zero instead of negative one and one.
所以你不能用 Math.sign 来确定这个
So you can't really use
Math.sign to determine this.
但如果你想自己做
But if you wanted to make your own,
在这里我用基本的方法来做我自己的工作
here I'm making my own by basically
fixing up the sign method.
我正在检查，在两个 0s 中的一个上，这就是第 8 行发生的事情。
And I'm checking if, on one of the two 0s,
that's what happens on line 8.
在两个 0s 中的一个上
And on one of the two 0s,
如果我不是两个人中的一个而不是我可以用这个符号
if I'm not one of the two
0srather than I can use the sign.
如果我是两个零中的一个，我就需要使用对象。如果我是 0，就想知道。
If I'm one of the two zeros, I need to
use object.is to figure out if I'm a -0.
所以这个固定签字的方法，你会在第 13 行通知下，
So that fixed up sign method,
you'll notice down there in line 13,
当有一个 -0时，它会返回 -1 。
it returns a -1 when there's a -0.
还有一种可能有用的方法让我们有一个符号的方法
So yet another way that it might be useful
for us to have a sign method that actually
这就是我们可以用一种有用的方式进行签名的方法。
works, and here's a way that we can make
a sign method that works in a useful way.
这也有原因
There's some reason for
在他们的回返值中有 0 到 0 但我觉得这很有用
the -0 thing in their return value,
but I don't think it's very useful.
好的，正如我所说的趋势。
Okay, so the trend example as I said.
趋势示例，
The trend example,
如果我想追踪某件事情的方向
if I wanted to keep track of what
direction something was moving.
比如这是个股票之类的我想继续追踪
Like if this was a stock or something
like that and I wanted to keep track of,
就算是零，它是在掉下去还是在上升呢 ?
even if it's at zero has it been
falling or has it been going up?
我想展示的是它是在下跌还是以股价上涨为例。
And I wanna show whether it's been falling
or rising in it's stock price for example.
在这里你会发现即使我追踪一个负的零我也可以证明
Where here you notice that even if I track
a negative zero I can show that it's been
掉到那个点了
falling at that point.
当它达到零值时，它就会上升。
As opposed to being rising when
it gets at the zero value.
那么，即使它们看起来有点细微差别，也会带来负面的负面影响，
So, negative zeros even though they seem
like they may be a little bit nuanced,
它们是语言中存在的值，您应该了解它们，并且
they're a value that exist in the language
so, you should know about them and
知道如何测试它们。
know how to test for them.
现在你知道他们存在了，你甚至可以找到他们的用途。
And now that you know that they exist, you
might even be able to find uses for them.
> > 学生: 对我来说，不是这样，还是很难
&gt;&gt; Student: For me it's not that,
it's still hard for
我和我比较清楚的是方向
me, and
I would rather define direction versus.
对我来说没有数学价值
For me it's hard there is no math value.
我的意思是，零的权利，它是一种支持它的语言。
I mean, zero zero right,
it's a language that supports it.
>> 凯尔 - 辛普森: 是的，我理解这个观点
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah,
I understand that perspective and
这完全是有效的但这对我来说
that's entirely valid,
but that's sounds to me
比如有人说我不关心负数字
like when somebody says I don't
care about negative numbers at all.
我只拥有拥有绝对价值的数字
I just have numbers that
have absolute values,
我用了没有符号的整数
I used unsigned integers or something.
签名号码是件事数学上也有问题
Signed numbers are a thing and
there a thing in math, so
如果数学中有一个东西，那么负零也是一个有用的东西。
if there's a thing in math then a negative
zero is also a thing that can be useful.
好了这些特殊的价值将会出现在我们的节目中
Okay, so those special values,
they're gonna occur in our programs,
并且对我们的计划中存在的类型和价值有敏锐的认识。
and having an acute awareness of types and
the values that can exist in our programs.
他们会帮助我们不仅避免虫子，还能更好地利用我们的工具。
They're gonna help us not only avoid bugs,
but also make better usage of our tool.
不仅能做点什么但也许能在语义上做些什么
Not only just be able to do something,
but maybe do something more semantically,
也许能让我们的代码更容易阅读或更容易理解
maybe make something that makes our code
more readable or more understandable.
我想说如果我使用阳性或
I would argue that it is much more
consistent if I'm using positive or
在我的正常号码中指示方向
negative in my regular numbers
to indicate direction,
我没有单独变量来跟踪零的方向
that I'll not have separate
variable to track zeros direction.
这对我来说更符合我的想法而且我觉得更能沟通的是代码
It's much more consistent to me, and
I think more communicative in code,
如果我用零的符号来指示方向
if I use the sign of the zero
to also indicate the direction.